<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Hugo Future Imperfect Slim</title>
    <link>https://hugo-future-imperfect-slim.netlify.app/</link>
    <description>Recent content on Hugo Future Imperfect Slim</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 19 Sep 2022 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://hugo-future-imperfect-slim.netlify.app/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Art</title>
      <link>https://hugo-future-imperfect-slim.netlify.app/art/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 28 Jun 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hugo-future-imperfect-slim.netlify.app/art/</guid>
      <description>Music Check out my band CD-ROM COM on Spotify, Apple Music, or YouTube.
Visual As of 2023, I don&amp;rsquo;t have a dedicated site yet for hosting my own photography, but check out my Instagram to see some of my landscape photography.
        A quote from Phil Tippett I photoshopped onto a panel from Calvin and Hobbes (All credits to Bill Watterson)    </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>&#34;You&#39;re Not Listening&#34; is the Most Important Book I&#39;ve Read this Year</title>
      <link>https://hugo-future-imperfect-slim.netlify.app/blog/youre_not_listening_review/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 19 Sep 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hugo-future-imperfect-slim.netlify.app/blog/youre_not_listening_review/</guid>
      <description>Every once in a while, someone writes something that punches me square in the chin and forces me to re-evaluate a critical part of how I see myself. The latest person to do that is Kate Murphy.
At the recommendation of a friend, I read her 2019 book “You’re Not Listening: What You’re Missing and Why It Matters” over the past week. Murphy’s pinpointed exactly what has felt wrong in most of my daily interactions for years: the prevalence of terrible listening patterns across many communities in the US.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Papers</title>
      <link>https://hugo-future-imperfect-slim.netlify.app/papers/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 30 Jan 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hugo-future-imperfect-slim.netlify.app/papers/</guid>
      <description>Here are some papers I&amp;rsquo;ve worked on from classes and my involvement in GT&amp;rsquo;s student government.
 Chicken Hero Ethics and Culture at Georgia Tech Deep Q-Networks with Prioritized Experience Replay  </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Trip to Seattle</title>
      <link>https://hugo-future-imperfect-slim.netlify.app/blog/seattle_january_2022/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 10 Jan 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hugo-future-imperfect-slim.netlify.app/blog/seattle_january_2022/</guid>
      <description>Just wrapped up visiting a few friends and checking out the city of Seattle for the first time. Here are some photos I took from across the city this weekend.
Scenery         View of Seattle from Kerry Park.            The same view of Seattle from Kerry Park, taken at night.            The Olympic Mountains as seen from Queen Anne.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Long-Form Diarization for Predicting Podcast Speakers</title>
      <link>https://hugo-future-imperfect-slim.netlify.app/projects/diarization/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 03 Jan 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hugo-future-imperfect-slim.netlify.app/projects/diarization/</guid>
      <description>About Speaker diarization is &amp;ldquo;the process of partitioning an input audio stream into homogeneous segments according to the speaker identity&amp;rdquo; (Wikipedia).
Plenty of services exist today for diarizing speakers at a local level: given an audio file, services such as AssemblyAI&amp;rsquo;s Speech-to-Text API, Amazon Transcribe, and Google&amp;rsquo;s Speech-to-Text can provide diarization for the speakers within that audio file.
As a machine learning engineering intern at SpareMin, I developed and prototyped what we believe to be the first service for diarizing speakers across entire podcast feeds.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>About Me</title>
      <link>https://hugo-future-imperfect-slim.netlify.app/about/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 17 Dec 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hugo-future-imperfect-slim.netlify.app/about/</guid>
      <description>Hello! Thanks so much for visiting my personal website!
I&amp;rsquo;m a software engineer at Flatiron Health and a recent graduate in Computer Science and Music Technology from Georgia Tech. I&amp;rsquo;m not currently looking for new full-time opportunities, but I&amp;rsquo;m always happy to connect with people working in technology, education, or music. A few ways you can reach me are:
 LinkedIn GitHub Twitter Email: cyheffley (at) gmail (dot) com  Resume For a copy of my resume, please email me at cyheffley (at) gmail (dot) com.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Contact Me</title>
      <link>https://hugo-future-imperfect-slim.netlify.app/contact/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 17 Dec 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hugo-future-imperfect-slim.netlify.app/contact/</guid>
      <description>You can contact me at cyheffley (at) gmail (dot) com, or connect with me on any of the social media below:
 LinkedIn GitHub Twitter  </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Course Critique</title>
      <link>https://hugo-future-imperfect-slim.netlify.app/projects/critique/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 22 Jun 2017 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hugo-future-imperfect-slim.netlify.app/projects/critique/</guid>
      <description>About Originally an annually-published book that dates back to at least the 1970&amp;rsquo;s, Course Critique is a static web application owned by Georgia Tech&amp;rsquo;s Student Government Association. Critique allows users to view historical course grade distributions across all instructors and courses offered at Georgia Tech.
I served in Georgia Tech&amp;rsquo;s SGA as team owner for Critique&amp;rsquo;s development team from 2018 until 2020, where I spent a year as SGA&amp;rsquo;s Vice President of IT, a role that involved a few policy-driven responsibilities in addition to overseeing maintenance and development for projects such as Critique.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>CyComics</title>
      <link>https://hugo-future-imperfect-slim.netlify.app/projects/cycomics/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 22 Jun 2017 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hugo-future-imperfect-slim.netlify.app/projects/cycomics/</guid>
      <description>About CyComics is a free subscription service for viewing daily comics through e-mail.
Subscribers can use a Google form to manage their personalized comics page and control which days of the week they receive comics in their inbox.
Currently, there are about 70 subscribers that can choose between about 75 different comics.
I built the first iteration of this project in an afternoon in 2020 while I was procrastinating on some schoolwork, but I&amp;rsquo;ve tinkered with the project on and off for general maintenance and optimizing for readability and scalability.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Microwaves at Tech</title>
      <link>https://hugo-future-imperfect-slim.netlify.app/projects/microwaves/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 22 Jun 2017 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hugo-future-imperfect-slim.netlify.app/projects/microwaves/</guid>
      <description>About Check out Find My Microwave here.
This website tracks microwave ovens across Georgia Tech so that students can burn popcorn and meet firefighters heat up food around campus. It&amp;rsquo;s built with Bootstrap and Google Maps&#39; Static API, and includes a form for submitting locations or feedback through e-mail.
This website was my first exposure to coding and was built in January 2017 at Georgia Tech&amp;rsquo;s HackGTeeny event.
You can check out our source code here.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Video Subtitle Bot [Inactive]</title>
      <link>https://hugo-future-imperfect-slim.netlify.app/projects/subtitle_bot/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 22 Jun 2017 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hugo-future-imperfect-slim.netlify.app/projects/subtitle_bot/</guid>
      <description>About This bot is no longer active due to another Twitter caption bot already being available: HeadlinerClip Caption.
When mentioned in reply to a video of up to 140 seconds long on Twitter, this bot would reply with an automatically-captioned copy of the video. Captioning was done with GCP Speech-to-Text, and our server was built using tweepy.
We additionally included a data integrity measure: every 10 minutes, all original video tweets were checked to ensure that they were still publicly accessible.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>https://hugo-future-imperfect-slim.netlify.app/projects/ethics/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://hugo-future-imperfect-slim.netlify.app/projects/ethics/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
